{"data":[{"question":"The following ___ some new popular love songs.","a":"is","b":"are","c":"were","d":"was","answer":"2","explain":"- Real subject is \"some new popular love songs\" which is plural \n- Simple present tense: use Simple Present to talk about scheduled events in the near future","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"37","type":"1"},{"question":"My family as well as I _________ glad to meet you.","a":"are","b":"am","c":"were","d":"is","answer":"1","explain":"\n-When using as well as, except, in addition to, no less than, and with, the noun before these phrases determines the number","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"37","type":"1"},{"question":"Neither he or I _________ for the decision.","a":"is","b":"are","c":"were","d":"am","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Not only. . .but also, and neither. . .nor:The subject closest to the verb determines whether the verb is singular or plural.","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"37","type":"1"},{"question":"Necessity ___ mother of invention.","a":"is","b":"are","c":"was","d":"were","answer":"1","explain":"- Necessity: singular noun \n- Simple present tense: express general facts","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"37","type":"1"},{"question":"Only one of the students in our school ___ awarded a copy of English-Chinese dictionary.","a":"has","b":"have","c":"is","d":"are","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Subject (only one) is singular noun \n- Present perfect:We use the Present Perfect to say that an action happened at an unspecified time before now ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"37","type":"1"},{"question":"Mathematics ___ the language of science.","a":"are going to be","b":"are","c":"is going to be","d":"is","answer":"4","explain":"- Subject (mathematics) is singular noun \n- Simple present tense: express general facts","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"37","type":"1"},{"question":"Taking a walk and going jogging ___ beneficial to your health.","a":"are","b":"is","c":"have proved to","d":"has been to","answer":"1","explain":"- Use a plural verb with two or more subjects when they are connected by and.","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"37","type":"1"},{"question":"___ hardworking people.","a":"Taiwanese is","b":"Taiwanese are","c":"The Taiwanese is","d":"The Taiwanese are","answer":"4","explain":"<p class=\"MsoNormal\" style=\"margin-bottom: 0.0001pt;\"><span style=\"font-family: Tahoma, sans-serif;\"><span style=\"font-size: 13.3333px; line-height: normal;\">-The + adjective: used before an adjective to make it into a plural noun when you are referring to all the people that the adjective describes\n<p class=\"MsoNormal\" style=\"margin-bottom: 0.0001pt;\"><span style=\"font-family: Tahoma, sans-serif;\"><span style=\"font-size: 13.3333px; line-height: normal;\">- The Taiwanese(= Taiwanese people) is plural\n\u00a0","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"37","type":"1"},{"question":"Plant ___ constant watering.","a":"needs","b":"need","c":"is needed","d":"are needed","answer":"1","explain":"\n- It is true in general","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"37","type":"1"},{"question":"That missing woman is the only target that the police ___.","a":"are after","b":"is after","c":"are looked for","d":"is looking for","answer":"1","explain":"- Be after somebody","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"37","type":"1"}]}